Macbeth Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence Files, 1838-1968, n.d., Series 1:; (Box 1-95, 163-164, OV 165; 96.2 linear feet)
  - Correspondence, 1838-1968, n.d., 1.1:
    - C. W. Parker & Co., 1899 (Box 17)
    - Cabell, Walter Coles and Charlotte R. (NMc31), 1919-1932 (Box 17)
    - Cadenasco, Guiseppe (NMc5), 1899, 1901 (Box 17)
    - Cadwalader, Lambert (NMc31), 1924-1925 (Box 17)
    - Cady, Harrison (2577), 1932-1933 (Box 17)
    - Cady, Henry N. (NMc5/NMc31), 1895-1908 (Box 17)
    - Cahill, A. M. (NMc5), 1908 (Box 17)
    - Cain, Harriet L. and Pinckney L. Cain (NMc31), 1923-1929 (Box 17)
    - Calahan, J. J. (NMc5), ca. 1895-1896 (Box 17)
    - Calder, A. Stirling (NMc5), 1910-1911 (Box 17)
    - Calder, William M. (NMc31), 1911, 1919 (Box 17)
    - Caldwell, Blanche F. (Mrs. Brown; NMc31), 1933 (Box 17)
    - Caldwell, Mrs. Charles (NMc31), 1917 (Box 17)
    - Caldwell, Eleanor B. (NMc5), 1895-1900 (Box 17)
    - Caldwell, John, 1894 (Box 17)
    - California Palace of the Legion of Honor (NMc31/2577), 1925-1951 (Box 17)
    - Caliga, I. H. (NMc5/NMc31), 1893-1925, n.d. (Box 17)
    - Call, Mary E. (NMc31), 1914-1915 (Box 17)
    - Calo Art Galleries (NMc31), 1924-1926, 1932 (Box 17)
    - Calvert, George C. (NMc31/2577), 1917-1948 (Box 17)
    - Camelback Galleries (2577), 1946-1953 (Box 17)
    - Cameron, James I. and Mrs. Cameron (NMc31), 1928-1933 (Box 17)
    - Campbell, Alice F. (NMc31), n.d. (Box 17)
    - Campbell, Blendon (NMc31), 1915-1933 (Box 17)
    - Campbell, Harry V. (2577), 1951-1963 (Box 17)
    - Campbell, Orland (NMc31/NMc44/2577), 1922-1925, n.d. (Box 17)
    - Campbell, William Raymond (2577), 1937, n.d. (Box 17)
    - Campion, W. P., 1911 (Box 17)
    - Canadian National Exhibition (NMc31/2577), 1909-1918 (Box 17)
    - Canajoharie Art Gallery (2577), 1937-1954, (3 folders) (Box 17)
    - Cannell and Chaffin, Inc. (NMc31/2577), 1920-1928, (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Cape Cod School of Art (NMc31), 1911-1913 (Box 18)
    - Cape Gallery (NMc31), 1929 (Box 18)
    - Capone, Gaetano (NMc31), 1914 (Box 18)
    - Carey, Laura (NMc31), 1928 (Box 18)
    - Carey Printing Company Inc. (NMc31/2577), 1917-1923, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Carhart, James L. (NMc31), 1914-1915 (Box 18)
    - Carkhuff, Stacy G. (NMc31/2577), 1917-1918 (Box 18)
    - Carl, Charles W. (2577), 1947 (Box 18)
    - Carlen Galleries (2577), 1956-1957, n.d. (Box 18)
    - Carlsen, Emil (NMc5/NMc31/NMc44/NMc48/2577), 1911-1929, n.d., (7 folders) (Box 18)
    - Carlsen, Emil, Estate (Dines Carlsen, Mary Carlsen; NMc5/NMc31/NMc44NMc48/2577), 1932-1937 (Box 18)
    - Carlson, John F. (NMc5/NMc31/2577), ca. 1912-1937, n.d., (10 folders) (Box 18)
    - Carlyle, Florence (NMc5), ca. 1906-1907 (Box 18)
    - Carnegie, Andrew, 1895 (Box 18)
    - Carnegie Corporation (NMc31), 1933 (Box 18)
    - Carnegie Institute (see also Box 163; NMc32/2577-2578), 1895-1919, (11 folders) (Box 18)
    - Carnegie Institute (NMc31/NMc32/2577-2578), 1920-1954, (17 folders) (Box 19)
    - Carnegie, Lucy C. (2578), 1906 (Box 19)
    - Carnegie Public Library (NMc32/2578), 1914-1932 (Box 19)
    - Carnegie, Mrs. S. M., 1893-1895 (Box 19)
    - Carolan, Harriet P. (Mrs. Francis; NMc32), 1922 (Box 19)
    - Carolina Art Association (NMc36), 1920-1921 (Box 19)
    - Carpenter, Frederick G. (NMc5), 1910 (Box 19)
    - Carpenter, H. Beach (NMc32), 1933 (Box 19)
    - Carpenter, Horace C. (Independence Hall), 1939 (Box 19)
    - Carpenter, J. S. and Mrs. Carpenter (NMc32/2578), 1914-1922 (Box 19)
    - Carper Galleries (NMc32/2578), 1919-1924 (Box 19)
    - Carrigan, George C. (NMc32), 1937 (Box 19)
    - Carrigan, William L. (NMc5/NMc32), 1911-1929 (Box 19)
    - Carrington, Edmund (NMc32), 1915 (Box 19)
    - Carrington, Fitz Roy (NMc32/2578), 1911-1924 (Box 19)
    - Carroll, Charles Gordon (NMc32), 1917-1926 (Box 19)
    - Carroll Galleries, Inc. (NMc32/2578), 1914-1916 (Box 19)
    - Carson, James Pettigru (NMc32/2578), 1918-1923 (Box 19)
    - Carson Pirie Scott & Co. (see also box 163; NMc32/2578), 1915-1932, (8 folders) (Box 19)
    - Carter, E. T. (NMc32), 1913 (Box 19)
    - Carter, John (NMc32/2578), 1926-1932 (Box 19)
    - Cary, Elisabeth Luther (NMc32), 1895-1914, 1921, 1932 (Box 19)
    - Cary, Evelyn Ramsey (Mrs. Charles; NMc32), 1912-1915 (Box 19)
    - Cary, Julia Metcalf (Mrs. M. B.; NMc32), 1915-1925, n.d. (Box 19)
    - Casamajor, Robert (2578), 1916-1921 (Box 19)
    - Case, Leland B. (NMc32), 1914-1915 (Box 19)
    - Caser, Ettore (NMc5/NMc32), 1912-1929 (Box 19)
    - Casey, George W. (NMc32), 1933 (Box 19)
    - Caspary, A. H. (NMc32/2578), 1932-1942 (Box 19)
    - Casson Galleries (see also box 163; NMc32/2578), 1924-1925, (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Casson Galleries (NMc32/2578), 1925-1933, (11 folders) (Box 20)
    - Castano, J., 1933 (Box 20)
    - Catlin, Arnold W. (NMc32), 1893-1917 (Box 20)
    - Catlin, Esther H. (Mrs. Robert M., Jr.; 2578), 1940-1941 (Box 20)
    - Cecil, Arthur B. (NMc32/2578), 1917-1932 (Box 20)
    - Cedar City Art Exhibit (2578), 1948-1951 (Box 20)
    - Cedar Rapids Art Association, 1926, 1932, 1947 (Box 20)
    - Cedarquist, A. E. (NMc32/2578), 1920-1933 (Box 20)
    - [Cellem?], Fred, 1893-1894 (Box 20)
    - Century Association (2578), 1896-1952 (Box 20)
    - Century Association, Asher B. Durand Exhibition (2578), 1942-1943 (Box 20)
    - Century Association, Henry Peters Gray Exhibition (2578), 1943 (Box 20)
    - Century Co. (NMc32), 1905-1926 (Box 20)
    - Chadbourne, Mrs. E. C. (2578), 1951-1957 (Box 20)
    - Chadbourne, Emily C. (2578), 1904-1905, 1918 (Box 20)
    - Chaffee, Mary D. (Mrs. Z; NMc32), 1928-1929 (Box 20)
    - Chamberlain, Linda E. (2578), 1912-1913, 1917 (Box 20)
    - Chamberlain, Mary (NMc32), 1919-1922 (Box 20)
    - Chambers, Eunice (NMc32/2578-2579), 1928, 1933-1962, (5 folders) (Box 20)
    - Chambers, Robert A. (NMc32/2579), 1926-1929 (Box 20)
    - Chambers, Mrs. Robert W. (2579), 1939 (Box 20)
    - Champeau, Lawrence X. (NMc32), 1914-1917, 1937 (Box 20)
    - Chandler, A. D'Alma (NMc36/2579), 1923-1937 (Box 20)
    - Chandler, H. Daland (2579), 1949 (Box 20)
    - Chandlers, Mrs. L. B. (NMc32/2579), 1916-1922 (Box 20)
    - Chanler, Ashley, 1950 (Box 20)
    - Chapin, H. W. and Lucy Grosvenor (NMc5), 1899 (Box 20)
    - Chapin, Horace D. (2579), 1936-1937 (Box 20)
    - Chapin, James and Louise (NMc32), 1933 (Box 20)
    - Chapin, William H. and Mrs. Chapin (NMc32/2579), 1912-1932 (Box 20)
    - Chapman, Albert K. (2579), 1949-1951 (Box 20)
    - Chapman, Alice G. (NMc32/2579), 1913-1926 (Box 20)
    - Chapman, Aurelié R. and Carlton T. Chapman (NMc5/NMc32/2579), ca. 1899-1900, 1925-1949 (Box 20)
    - Chapman, Henry T. and Estate (NMc32/2579), 1894-1914 (Box 20)
    - Chapman, W. P., Jr. (NMc32), 1914, 1926-1929 (Box 20)
    - Chappel, Mary R. (Mrs. Henry W.), 1933 (Box 20)
    - Charcoal Club (NMc32), 1911-1924 (Box 20)
    - Charles E. Lauriat Company, 1905, 1918, n.d. (Box 20)
    - Charles H. Lee Mail Service, Inc., 1924-1925 (Box 20)
    - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1895-1932, (3 folders) (Box 20)
    - Charles, T. T. (NMc32), 1917-1921 (Box 20)
    - Charlestown Library Society, 1914 (Box 20)
    - Chase, Ethel (NMc32), 1925-1928 (Box 20)
    - Chase, Frank Swift (see also box 163; NMc32/NMc36), ca. 1913-1928, n.d. (Box 20)
    - Chase, J. Eastman (NMc35/NMc36/2579), 1898-1903, 1915 (Box 20)
    - Chase, Rodney (NMc32), 1928-1932 (Box 20)
    - Chase, Sidney M. (NMc32), 1914, 1929-1932 (Box 20)
    - Chase, William Merritt and Mrs. Chase (NMc5/NMc32), 1906-1929 (Box 20)
    - Chattanooga Art Association (NMc36), 1928, 1949 (Box 20)
    - Chatterton, Clarence K. (NMc32/2579), 1919-1937, 1947, (3 folders) (Box 21)
    - Chauvignand, George (NMc5), 1899 (Box 21)
    - Cheever, Elizabeth S. (NMc32/NMc33), 1896-1924 (Box 21)
    - Cheffetz, Asa (NMc32), 1932-1933 (Box 21)
    - Cheney, Edith S. (Mrs. Wallace; 2579), 1943-1953 (Box 21)
    - Cheney, Lillian F. (see also box 163; Mrs. B. A.; NMc33/2579), 1921-1925 (Box 21)
    - Chicago Evening Post (NMc33/2579), 1924-1926 (Box 21)
    - Chicago Examiner (2579), 1916-1926 (Box 21)
    - Chicago Galleries Association (NMc33), 1928 (Box 21)
    - Chicago Herald Examiner (NMc33), 1923-1926 (Box 21)
    - Chicago Historical Society (2579), 1941, 1954 (Box 21)
    - Chicago Norske Klub (NMc33), 1926 (Box 21)
    - Chichester, Cecil (NMc33/2579), 1912-1944, n.d., (3 folders) (Box 21)
    - Child, Edwin B. (NMc5/NMc33), 1893, 1917-1929, n.d. (Box 21)
    - Children's Welfare Federation of New York City, Inc. (NMc33), 1933 (Box 21)
    - Childs, Charles D. (NMc36/2579), 1937-1952 (Box 21)
    - Childs, Eversley (NMc33/2579), 1913-1920 (Box 21)
    - Childs, William Hamlin (NMc33/2579), 1909-1929 (Box 21)
    - Chiles, Jane M. (NMc33), 1928-1929 (Box 21)
    - Chittenden, Adelaide C., 1914 (Box 21)
    - Choate, Mary P. (Mrs. A.C.C.; NMc33), 1917 (Box 21)
    - Christensen, Florence (NMc33), 1923-1924 (Box 21)
    - Christian, George C. (NMc36/2579), 1916 (Box 21)
    - Christian Science Monitor (NMc33/2579), 1911-1928, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 21)
    - Christophe, M. Therese (NMc33), 1933 (Box 21)
    - Church, Elliott B. (NMc33), 1922-1933 (Box 21)
    - Church, Frederick Stuart (see also box 163; NMc5/2579), 1893-1915, n.d., (illustrated letters 4/22/09, 5/31/12) (Box 21)
    - Church, Katharine C. (NMc33/2579), 1917-1940, n.d. (Box 21)
    - Churchill, Alfred Vance (NMc33), 1913-1914, 1922 (Box 21)
    - Cincinnati Art Museum (2579), 1932-1954 (Box 21)
    - Cincinnati Museum Association (NMc33/2579-2580), 1895-1932, (11 folders) (Box 21)
    - Circuit Exhibitions (NMc33/2579-2580), ca. 1924-1926 (Box 21)
    - Circuit Exhibitions, Colorado (NMc33/2579-2580), 1924-1925 (Box 21)
    - Circuit Exhibitions, Illinois (NMc33/2579-2580), 1924-1928, (3 folders) (Box 21)
    - Circuit Exhibitions, Iowa (NMc33/2579-2580), 1924-1926, (4 folders) (Box 21)
    - Circuit Exhibitions, Nebraska (NMc33/2579-2580), 1925 (Box 21)
    - Circuit Exhibitions, Texas (NMc33/2579-2580), 1924 (Box 21)
    - Circuit Exhibitions, Wyoming (NMc33/2579-2580), 1924-1925 (Box 21)
    - City Club of New York (see also box 163; NMc36/2580), 1910-1915 (Box 21)
    - Citizens Union of the City of New York, 1913-1914 (Box 21)
    - City Art Museum of St. Louis, 1895-1915, (3 folders; includes illustrated letter from Charles Ward Rhodes, 5/22/99) (Box 21)
    - City Art Museum of St. Louis, 1916-1954, (8 folders) (Box 22)
    - City of New York, 1935-1940 (Box 22)
    - Civic Club of Carlisle, 1926-1928 (Box 22)
    - Claggett, Mrs. Wilson P. (NMc36/2580), 1929-1951 (Box 22)
    - Clapp & Graham Company, Inc. (NMc36), 1919-1920 (Box 22)
    - Clapp, W. M. (NMc33/2580), 1912-1921 (Box 22)
    - Clare J. Hoffman, Incorporated, 1927, 1952-1953 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Alson Skinner (NMc5/NMc33/2580), 1905-1920 (Box 22)
    - Clark, De Witt A. and Elizabeth De Witt Clark (see also box 163; NMc33/2580), 1915-1919, (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Clark, Eliot (NMc5/NMc33/2580), ca. 1908-1925, 1947 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Elizabeth (Mrs. George M.; 2580), 1916 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Emily J. (NMc33/NMc36/2580), 1914-1929, (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Clark, F. Ambrose (2580), 1942-1957 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Frances and Franklin B. Clark (NMc36), 1920-1923 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Frank H. (NMc33), 1914-1923 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Frederick H. (NMc5/NMc34), 1899-1907, 1926-1928 (Box 22)
    - Clark, George C. and Mrs. Clark (NMc34/2580), 1917-1932 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Mrs. H. L. (NMc34), 1929 (Box 22)
    - Clark, James L. (NMc36/2580), 1921-1922 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Marjorie (Mrs. Bruce; NMc33/NMc36), 1928-1933 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Nelson (NMc34), 1932, n.d. (Box 22)
    - Clark, Rose (NMc5/NMc34), 1896-ca. 1912, n.d., (2 folders) (Box 22)
    - Clark, Stephen C. (NMc34/2580), 1912-1962, (5 folders) (Box 22)
    - Clark, Virginina (Mrs. Marshall; NMc36), 1925-1926 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Walter and Mrs. Clark (NMc5/NMc36), ca. 1893-1896 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Walter H. (NMc34/NMc36), 1925-1929 (Box 22)
    - Clark, Walter L. (NMc36/2580), 1916-1922 (Box 22)
    - Clark, William A. (NMc36/2580), 1897-1925 (Box 22)
    - Clarke, Henry Martyn (2580), 1920 (Box 22)
    - Clarke, Hope Gorham (Mrs. Parker), 1922-1923 (Box 22)
    - Clarke, James H. (NMc36/2580), 1916-1919 (Box 22)
    - Clarke, Thomas B. (see also box 163; 2580), 1892-1893, 1907-1929, (3 folders) (Box 22)
    - Clarkson, Grosvenor B. (NMc36), 1921-1924, 1932 (Box 22)
    - Clearwater Art Museum (2580), 1946-1951 (Box 22)
    - Cleland, Roby, 1929 (Box 22)
    - Clements, George H. and Mrs. Clements (NMc34), 1919-1923 (Box 22)
    - Cleveland Art Loan Exposition (NMc34), 1913-1914 (Box 22)
    - Cleveland Institute of Art (NMc34/NMc36/2580), 1947-1953 (Box 22)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art (see also box 163; NMc34/2580), 1914-1957, (10 folders) (Box 22)
    - Clewell Studios (NMc34), 1928-1929 (Box 22)
    - Clifford, F. J. (NMc34/2580), 1921-1924 (Box 22)
    - Cline, I. M. (NMc34), 1914-1922 (Box 23)
    - Clinton, George, Jr. (2580), 1941 (Box 23)
    - Clise, J. W. (NMc34), 1914, 1919 (Box 23)
    - Closson, A. B. (NMc36/2580), 1929-1933 (Box 23)
    - Closson, William Baxter (NMc5/NMc34/NMc44), 1898-1921, (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Clover Club (NMc36), 1910-1915, n.d. (Box 23)
    - Clover, Henry A., 1910, 1920 (Box 23)
    - Coale, Griffith Baily (2580), 1937-1940 (Box 23)
    - Coale, Walter (NMc5), 1900-1901 (Box 23)
    - Coan, Titus M. (NMc36), 1909-1918 (Box 23)
    - Cobb, Charles E. (NMc36), 1902-1922 (Box 23)
    - Cobb, Katharine (Mrs. D. R.; NMc34), 1927-1929 (Box 23)
    - Coburn, Frederick W. (2580), 1946-1947 (Box 23)
    - Cochran, Allen D. (see also box 163; NMc34/2580), 1913-1917 (Box 23)
    - Cochran, Thomas (NMc34/2580-2581), 1928-1929, 1933, (13 folders) (Box 23)
    - Cochran, Thomas, Estate (NMc24/2580-2581), 1937-1941 (Box 23)
    - Cochrane, Constance (NMc34), 1922-1926 (Box 23)
    - Cochrane, Josephine G. (NMc5), ca. 1911-1913 (Box 23)
    - Coe, Ralph M. (NMc36/2581), 1915-1921, 1950-1952 (Box 23)
    - Coffin, Edward Francis (see also box 163; NMc34/2581) 1914-1948 (Box 23)
    - Coffin, Esther L. (NMc5), 1894, 1911 (Box 23)
    - Coffin, Sarah Faber (NMc5/NMc36), 1902 (Box 23)
    - Coffin, William A. (NMc5/NMc36), 1893-1917 (Box 23)
    - Coffin, Winthrop (NMc34/NMc36), 1911-1916 (Box 23)
    - Cogswell, Arnold (2581), 1954 (Box 23)
    - Cogswell, Charles N. (St. Botolph Club; NMc36), 1916-1917 (Box 23)
    - Cogswell, Ledyard, Jr., and Dorothy A. Cogswell (2581), 1951-1954 (Box 23)
    - Cohen, Katherine M. (NMc5), 1900-1903 (Box 23)
    - Cohen, M. H. (NMc34/2581), 1924-1932 (Box 23)
    - Cohen, Nessa (NMc34), 1914-1926 (Box 23)
    - Cohn, Mrs. Morris, Jr. (2581), 1909-1916 (Box 23)
    - Colby College (2581), 1954, 1963 (Box 23)
    - Cole, Annette Cole III and Thomas Cole III, 1952-1953 (Box 23)
    - Cole, L. B. (NMc34), 1919 (Box 23)
    - Cole, Philip G. (NMc34/2581), 1923-1933, (2 folders) (Box 23)
    - Cole, Philip R., 1937, 1942 (Box 23)
    - Cole, Thomas and Timothy Cole (NMc5/NMc34/NMc36), 1892, 1917-1918 (Box 23)
    - Coleman, Georgia H. (2581), 1956 (Box 23)
    - Coles, Ann Cadwallader (NMc5/NMc34), 1912-1914 (Box 23)
    - Coles Electrical Company (NMc34/NMc36), 1924 (Box 23)
    - Coll, A. P. (NMc34), 1915-1921 (Box 23)
    - Collector/Collector and Art Critic, 1895-1907 (Box 23)
    - College Art Association (NMc34/2581), 1929-1933, (3 folders) (Box 23)
    - Collins, Adah B (Mrs. J. J.; NMc34), 1929, 1933 (Box 23)
    - Collins Art Co. (NMc34), 1933, 1937 (Box 23)
    - Collins, Mary Barrow (2581), 1932 (Box 23)
    - Collins, Will F. (NMc34), 1927-1928 (Box 23)
    - Colman, Samuel (NMc5), 1893, 1903, 1905 (Box 23)
    - Colorado Museum of Natural History, 1910 (Box 24)
    - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center (2581), 1947-1953 (Box 24)
    - Colter, Mrs. A. W. (NMc34), 1922-1924 (Box 24)
    - Columbia Museum of Art, 1950-1955 (Box 24)
    - Columbia University Alumni Federation Decennial Committee, 1916 (Box 24)
    - Columbia University and Alumni Club (see also box 163; 2581), 1895-1937, (23 folders) (Box 24)
    - Columbia University and Alumni Club, New Jersey Chapter (2582), 1932, 1951, (2 folders) (Box 24)
    - Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgeons, 1926-1928 (Box 24)
    - Columbus Art Association, 1904, 1910 (Box 24)
    - Columbus Gallery of Fine Arts (NMc34/NMc36/2582), 1909-1910, 1923-1951, (4 folders) (Box 24)
    - Coman, Charlotte Buell (see also box 163; NMc5/NMc6/NMc34/2582), 1893-1926, n.d., (6 folders; 1920 includes an illustrated Christmas card from Coman) (Box 25)
    - Combe, Amy, 1908-1910 (Box 25)
    - Compera, Alexis (NMc5), 1892-1906 (Box 25)
    - Compton, Jean H. (Mrs. William P.; 2582), 1937, 1943 (Box 25)
    - Comstock, Margaret B. (2582), 1937 (Box 25)
    - Concord Art Association, Inc. (NMc34/2582), 1916-1923 (Box 25)
    - Condé Nast Publications (2582), 1917-1926, 1947-1948 (Box 25)
    - Congdon, Clarence S. (2582), 1937 (Box 25)
    - Congdon, Thomas R. (NMc6), 1912 (Box 25)
    - Conklin, R. H. (NMc34), 1922-1929 (Box 25)
    - Conn, C. G. (NMc34), 1914-1915 (Box 25)
    - Connaway, Jay (NMc34/2582), 1923-1928, n.d. (Box 25)
    - Connaway, Jay and Louise Connaway (NMc34/2582), 1928-1939, 1947-1953, (6 folders; 1932 includes a photograph of the Connaway's daughter Leonebel) (Box 25)
    - Connecticut College (2582), 1925 (Box 25)
    - Connecticut State Normal- Training School, 1908-1914 (Box 25)
    - Conner, Florence (Mrs. William A.; NMc35), 1933 (Box 25)
    - Consolidated Appraisal Co., Inc. (NMc35/NMc36), 1921-1924 (Box 25)
    - Constance, Caroline (2582), 1918 (Box 25)
    - Contemporary Arts, 1932-1944 (Box 25)
    - Cook, Arthur B. (2582), 1906-1908 (Box 25)
    - Cook, Catherine (NMc35), 1933 (Box 25)
    - Cook, Clarence (NMc6), 1896, 1900 (Box 25)
    - Cook, Earl (NMc36/2582), 1955 (Box 25)
    - Cook, Jean Berman (NMc6), 1906, n.d. (Box 25)
    - Cook, John A. (NMc36), 1929-1933 (Box 25)
    - Cook, Mrs. William I. and R. E. Nail (NMc35-36), 1928-1932 (Box 25)
    - Cooke, Robert Grier (Fifth Avenue Association), 1905-1911 (Box 25)
    - Coolidge, T. Jefferson (Estate), 1921 (Box 25)
    - Cooper, Colin Campbell (NMc35), 1914-1918 (Box 25)
    - Cooper, Mrs. Elisha H. (NMc35), 1926, 1928 (Box 25)
    - Cooper, Elizabeth (2582), 1918, 1948 (Box 25)
    - Cooper, James Fenimore (NMc36), 1914, 1916 (Box 25)
    - Cooper Union Museum (2582), 1937-1949 (Box 25)
    - Cooper, W. A. (NMc36/2582), 1896-1912 (Box 25)
    - Cooperative G.L.F. Exchange, Inc. (2582), 1947 (Box 25)
    - Copeland, Lucien B. (NMc35), 1928 (Box 25)
    - Copley Society of Boston, 1904 (Box 25)
    - Copp, James D. (NMc36/2582), 1913, 1925, 1939 (Box 25)
    - Copp, Marie T. (NMc36), 1953 (Box 25)
    - Coppedge, Fern I. (NMc35), 1926 (Box 25)
    - Corbett, George J. (2582), 1948-1949 (Box 25)
    - Corbett, Helen Ladd (NMc35/2582), 1908, 1913-1924, (6 folders) (Box 25)
    - Corbino, Jon (NMc35/2582), 1937, n.d. (Box 25)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1906-1925, (8 folders) (Box 25)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art (NMc35/2582), 1926-1956, (8 folders) (Box 26)
    - Cornelius, Brother (NMc36), 1933, 1937 (Box 26)
    - Cornell, Milton L. (NMc35), 1929 (Box 26)
    - Cornell University (NMc35-36), 1913-1928, 1950-1954 (Box 26)
    - Cornell University Library, 1919 (Box 26)
    - Corner, Thomas C. (NMc36/2582), 1912-1920, 1933 (Box 26)
    - Cornoyer, Paul (NMc35/2582), 1914-1920 (Box 26)
    - Corse, Mrs. Frederick W. (NMc35), 1923 (Box 26)
    - Cortissoz, Royal (NMc35/NMc36/2582), 1908-1937, (4 folders) (Box 26)
    - Cory, James (NMc35), 1912-1933 (Box 26)
    - Cosden, Alfred H. (NMc35), 1914, 1916 (Box 26)
    - Cosgrave, Esta (Mrs. John O'Hara II), 1944, 1950, n.d. (Box 26)
    - Costigan, John E. (NMc35/2582), 1928-1933 (Box 26)
    - Cottier & Co., 1906-1907 (Box 26)
    - Coulon, George A., 1897-1906 (Box 26)
    - Coulter, Mary J. (NMc36), 1928 (Box 26)
    - Country Life (NMc35/2582), 1914-1928 (Box 26)
    - County Clerk's Office, County of New York, 1919-1932 (Box 26)
    - Couse, E. Irving (NMc6/NMc35/2582), 1902, 1912-1929 (Box 26)
    - Cowan, James M. (NMc35), 1922, 1925 (Box 26)
    - Cowie Galleries (2582), 1933, 1948-1953 (Box 26)
    - Cowles, Maude Alice (NMc6), 1899-1900 (Box 26)
    - Cowles, Russel A. (NMc35), 1928, 1948, n.d. (Box 26)
    - Cox, Albert Scott (NMc6/NMc36), 1903, 1911-1915 (Box 26)
    - Cox, Hermine M., 1951, 1953 (Box 26)
    - Cox, Kenyon (NMc6), 1900-1902, 1916 (Box 26)
    - Coxe, Reginald Cleveland (NMc35), 1911-1917 (Box 26)
    - Coykendall, Edward (NMc35/2582), 1920-1933 (Box 26)
    - Coykendall, Frederick (NMc36), 1916-1937 (Box 26)
    - Crafts, William (2583), 1925 (Box 26)
    - Craig, Anne T. (NMc6), 1901 (Box 26)
    - Craig, Lily, Estate, and Lowry Craig (2583), 1925, 1937 (Box 26)
    - Craighead, Fannie M. (Mrs. Frank W.), 1922-1924 (Box 26)
    - Crane, Bruce (NMc6/NMc35/2583), 1892, 1915-1928, (3 folders) (Box 26)
    - Crane, Frederick and Mrs. Crane (NMc6/NMc35/NMc36), 1912-1917 (Box 26)
    - Crane, J. E. (NMc35), 1919 (Box 26)
    - Cranmer, Clarence W. (Poor Richard Club; NMc35/2583), 1928-1942, (3 folders) (Box 26)
    - Cranmer, Frances (NMc35), 1913 (Box 26)
    - Crary, Clare J. and Irene H. (NMc35/2583), 1913-1933 (Box 26)
    - Crawford, Earl Stetson (NMc6/NMc36), 1908-1923 (Box 26)
    - Crawford, John List (2583), 1913-1918 (Box 26)
    - Crawford, Laura (Mrs. Robert A.; NMc35/NMc36), 1928-1929 (Box 26)
    - Creative Art (NMc35), 1928-1933 (Box 26)
    - Creelman, Alice B. (Mrs. James; NMc36/2583), 1913-1918, 1928 (Box 26)
    - Creighton, Mrs. E. A. (2583), 1950, 1959 (Box 26)
    - Cresmer, William T. (NMc35/2583), 1914-1946, (4 folders) (Box 26)
    - Crimmins, John D. (NMc36), 1895-1917 (Box 26)
    - Crisis (W.E.B. DuBois), 1920 (Box 26)
    - Crisp, Arthur (NMc35), 1914-1928, n.d. (Box 26)
    - Crittenden, Lillian H. and Walter H. Crittenden (see also Brooklyn Museum; NMc35/NMc36/2583), 1903, 1911-1937, (2 folders) (Box 26)
    - Crittenden, Walter H. (see also Brooklyn Museum; NMc35/2583), 1923-1937 (Box 26)
    - Crittenden, Willard S. (NMc35), 1913-1917 (Box 26)
    - Crocker, Charles M. (NMc6/NMc36), 1910-1932, n.d. (Box 27)
    - Cronyn & Lowndes (NMc35), 1933 (Box 27)
    - Crosby, Percy, 1933 (Box 27)
    - Crossett, Elisabeth R. (Mrs. Edward C.; NMc36), 1923, 1951 (Box 27)
    - Crossman, Margaret R. (NMc35), 1926 (Box 27)
    - Crossroads of Sport, Inc. (2583), 1939-1950 (Box 27)
    - Croughton, G. Hanmer (NMc6), 1895 (Box 27)
    - Crowley, Herbert (NMc6), n.d., (1 illustrated letter) (Box 27)
    - Cudney, Ralph (NMc35/2583), 1914-1919, 1932 (Box 27)
    - Culver, Charles (2583), 1947-1953, (4 folders; see also OV 165 for illustrated letter 10/5/49; 1948-1951 include illustrated letters; 1951 includes catalog of Culver exhibition at Macbeth Gallery) (Box 27)
    - Cuming, Beatrice L. (NMc35), 1926-1928 (Box 27)
    - Cummer, Mrs. Arthur Gerish (2583), 1946-1954 (Box 27)
    - Cummer, Mrs. W. E. (NMc35), 1917, 1928 (Box 27)
    - Cummings, Mrs. J. J. (NMc35), 1922-1925 (Box 27)
    - Cunningham, Mrs. Alan (2583), 1942-1944 (Box 27)
    - Cunningham, Mrs. Alexander J. (NMc35), 1926 (Box 27)
    - Cunningham, William Allan (NMc35), 1915, 1918 (Box 27)
    - Curlander, Edward H. (NMc35/2583), 1924-1932 (Box 27)
    - Curran, Charles C. (NMc35), 1901-1933 (Box 27)
    - Curran, Mrs. W. B. (NMc35), 1929 (Box 27)
    - Currier, Bertram (NMc35), 1924 (Box 27)
    - Currier Gallery of Art (NMc35/2583), 1932-1958, (3 folders) (Box 27)
    - Curtis and Cameron Incorporated (see also box 163; NMc35-36/2583-2584), 1908-1933, (3 folders) (Box 27)
    - Curtis, F. Kingsbury (NMc36), 1916, 1928-1929 (Box 27)
    - Curtis, Fosdick & Belknap (2584), 1925 (Box 27)
    - Curtis, Ida Maynard (NMc36), 1917-1924 (Box 27)